Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 49, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Merit Rating Manual, Publication (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Summer Program For College Students: One Year Removed From Degree, Publication (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Summer Program Recruiting Manual, Publication (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: College Recruiting Manual 1953-54, Publication (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Box: 49, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Summer Employment Programs, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Technical Management, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Technical Career Paths, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Careers in Business and Technical Management, 1970; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Management Audit, 1957; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: An Overall Look at Management Development: A talk to the Training Within Industry Foundation, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
    Author: J.G. Pleasants
  - Item 7: Career Opportunities with Procter & Gamble's Advertising Department, 1957; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: Development Plan of the Case Goods Sales Department - A Guide in Selecting and Training Managerial Talent, 1936; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: District Instructor's Manual: A Guide in Training Salesmen, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Printer's Ink - Case History: Labor Relations, 1948; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 11: Summer Training in Industry, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: The Corporate Director - A Management Audit, 1952; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 13: Management Audit - The Procter & Gamble Company, 1957; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 14: Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Item 15: Physical Examination Procedure for Procter & Gamble Examiners, 1960; Publication (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Box: 49, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Procter & Gamble Stock Purchase Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: The Procter & Gamble Profit Sharing Dividend Plan, 1956; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Disability Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Procter & Gamble Disability Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: The Procter & Gamble Pension Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: The Procter & Gamble Group Life Insurance Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 9: Stock Purchase Plan, Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 10: The Procter & Gamble Program of Aid to Higher Education, 1961; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Item 11: The Procter & Gamble Program of Aid to Higher Education, 1957; Publication (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Box: 50, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Management Indoctrination Course, Publication (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Box: 50, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Management Indoctrination Course - The Review of Progress, Publication (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Box: 50, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Management Indoctrination Course: Handling Commendations, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Junior Engineer Training Program, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Increasing Your Retirement and Other Income, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Author: Norman D. Ford
  - Item 4: Retirement Preparation: Health Maintenance, Financial Planning, Retirement Activities, Psychological Aspects, Social Security, Prudential Benefits, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Retirement Preparation: Health Maintenance, Financial Planning, Retirement Activities, Psychological Aspects, Social Security, Prudential Benefits, Publication (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Box: 50, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Field Clerical Personnel Manual for District Agencies, 1949; Publication (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Box: 50, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization: Company, Corporate Services Area, Insurance Area, Investment Area, Planning and Control Area, CHO, EHO, MAHO, NCHO, NEHO, SCHO, SWHO, WHO, Committees, Publication (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Box: 50, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Insurance, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Revised Group Major Medical Expense Insurance, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: At No Cost to You - Polio Expense Benefits for You and Your Dependents, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Careers at the Prudential Home Office in Newark, N.J., Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: My Name is Jean, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Employee Development through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Salary Plan For Field Office Employees in the United States, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Salary Plan For Home Office Employees, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Dial 3204, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: You and Prudential, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Youand Prudential, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: The Prudential Way, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Management Digest, 1964; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Employee Development through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Is Life Insurance Too Big?, 1949; Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
    Author: Carrol M. Shanks
  - Item 16: Syllabus of Educational Courses I And II, 1949-1950 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Employee Benefits - Home Office Employees with Continuous Service Beginning on or After January 1, 1947, Publication (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Box: 50, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A Digest of the Principles and Techniques of Supervision, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: A Digest of the Principles and Techniques of Supervision, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: The Prudential Advanced Management Program, 1961; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Are You the One?, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Employee Development through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Our 75th Year of Service, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Good Citizen, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: You and Prudential, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: The Prudential Actuarial Training Program, Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Management Digest, 1967; Publication (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Box: 50, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Manager's Personnel Record Card, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Group Hospital, Surgical and Medical Expense Plan Enrollment Card, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Prudential Contributory Group Life Insurance and Retirement Plans, Enrollment Card, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Save for a sunny daywith U.S. Savings Bonds Dryden Memorial Library bookmark, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Letter re Suggestions from Carol M. Shanks, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Suggestion Form, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Group Major Medical Expense Records, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Doe John - A11, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Security for You and Your Family: Benefit Plans for District Agents of the Prudential Insurance Company of America, Publication (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Box: 50, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: You and Prudential, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Opportunity and Security with the Prudential, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Military Service Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Author: Carol M. Shanks
  - Item 4: A New Approach to Employee Counseling, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
    Author: John A. Bromer
  - Item 5: Notice, 1965; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Security for You and Your Family, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: For the Retirement Time of Your Life, 1953; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Revised Group Major Medical Expense Insurance, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Now-for-you Group Major Medical Expense Insurance, Publication (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Box: 50, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Field Management Digest, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: New Career Horizons: The Prudential insurance Company of America, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Summer Indoctrination Program for Male College Juniors, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Prudential's Economic Forecast 1964, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Effective Writing Techniques: Session I, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: POG Service Awards, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Job Opportunities at the Prudential for 1954 High School Graduates, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Opportunities for College Graduate Women, 1954; Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: A Job at The Pru is a Good Job in 1959, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Job Evaluation Manual, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: The Field Supervisors' Conferences, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: How Prudential Insurance Runs an "Effective Speaking Course", Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: How Prudential Insurance Runs an "Effective Speaking" Course, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Writing Yardstick: A Tool for More Effective Bargaining, Publication (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Box: 50, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: A Full Life After 65, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Author: Edith M. Stern
  - Item 2: Making the Most of Your Years, 1958; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Author: Evelyn Hart
  - Item 3: When You Grow Older, 1960; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Author: George Lawton and Maxwell S. Stewart
  - Item 4: Hazard Hunting, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: A Full Life After 65, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Food Guide for Older Folks, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: 16th Edition of Hobby Publications, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Eat and Grow Slim, 1959; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Where to Retire on a Small Income, 1964; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Food Guide for Older Folks, 1963; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Reader's Digest Reprint: Can Your Wife Afford to Be a Widow?, 1965; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Author: Frank J. Taylor
  - Item 12: Health Insurance for People 65 or Older, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: 18th Edition of Hobby Publications, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: If You Become Disabled, 1965; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: When You Grow Older, 1960; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Getting Ready to Retire, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
    Author: Kathryn Close
  - Item 17: Making the Most of Your Years, 1958; Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Harvest Years: Retirement Planning - in Retirement PlanningWhat you don't know can hurt you, Publication (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Box: 50, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Tomorrow's Secretary, 1966; Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Tomorrow's Secretary, 1957; Publication (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Box: 50, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Employee Development Through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Employee Development Through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Box: 50, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Employee Development through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Employee Development through Performance Review, Publication (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Box: 50, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Safety Bulletin, 1956; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: The Procter & Gamble Profit Sharing Dividend Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: The Procter & Gamble Profit Sharing Trust Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: My Pay At P&G, 1951; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Guaranteed Employment Plan, Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Time Bonus, 1962; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: The Procter & Gamble Time Bonus Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet: Procter & Gamble's Guaranteed Employment Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Box: 50, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A Progress Report on the Profit Sharing Research Foundation, 1956; Publication (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Box: 51, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Scale Data Book, Publication (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Box: 51, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Seminar Announcement: Recruitment and Selection in the Public Service, 1965; Publication (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Box: 51, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Welfare Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Box: 51, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Special Safety Instructions for Cranemen and Hookons, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: General Safety Instructions and Information, 1966; Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: General Safety Instructions and Information, 1952; Publication (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Box: 51, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Labor Relation Institute, Publication (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Box: 51, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Information for Managers and Supervisors, Publication (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Box: 51, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Information for Managers and Supervisors, Publication (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Box: 51, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: This is the Story of Your Quaker Benefits - for salaried employees of The Quaker Oats Company, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Quaker Retirement Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Consider the Difference at Quaker, Publication (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Box: 51, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Documentary Material on File at the Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Holidays, 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Quaker Oats Company Material Rec'd 3/16/55, 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Pensions, 1955; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Checklist of Material Needed on Company Industrial Relations Activities, 1950; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: A Standard List of Subject Headings in Industrial Relations, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Production Department Supervisory and Executive Development Program, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Production Department Supervisory and Executive Development Program, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Management Development, 1952; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Author: Ralph M. Hartmann
  - Item 10: Management Survey Experience Record, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Functional Chart, 1953; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Vacation Advice - Salaried Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Quaker Oats Company Social Progress Plan for Fiscal 1973, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: A Program of Aid To Higher Education, 1962; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: 1969 Annual Safety Report, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 16: Three Months' Follow-up of Salaried Employee, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Otis Self-Administering Tests of Mental Ability, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Author: Arthur S. Otis
  - Item 18: Vacation Advice - Salaried Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Personal History and Employment Application, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Vacation Advice - Salaried Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: Documentary Material on File at the industrial Relations Section, 1951-1952 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Documentary Material on File at the Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: Documentary Material on File at the Industrial Relations Section, Publication (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Box: 51, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Information for Managers and Supervisors, 1959; Publication (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Box: 51, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A New Helping HandQuaker's Illness and Accident Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Your Retirement Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Quaker's Guaranteed Work Plan for Employment Security, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: The Quaker Hospital Care Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: The Quaker Hospital Care Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Annual Report, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Management Development, 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Your Profit-Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: management Development, 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: You..and the RCA Retirement Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: The Salary Administration Program, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: The Career Opportunity Program, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Your Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Building Together for Your Retirement, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Your Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Your Retirement Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Your Health Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Your Profit-Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Retirement Annuity Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Your Health Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Employees' Wage Bonus Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: You and Flextime, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 23: The Quaker Oats Company Annual Report 1972, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: Pensions, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: The Quaker Oats Company Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 26: Plan for Progress, 1969; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Item 27: The New York Society of Security Analysts, 1969; Publication (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Box: 51, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Guide For Management, Publication (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Box: 51, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: More Help with the Bills Through the New Quaker Major Medical Plan, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Job Evaluation Handbook, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Vacation Advice - Salaried Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Management Appraisal, 1956; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Appraisal Summary, Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Instructions - Feed Sales Appraisal and Development Program, 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Performance Review - Coaching Subordinates, 1957; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Annual Safety Report 1957, 1958; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Reference Materials Available from Training Office covering such subjects as Training, Production Operations, Employee & Public Relations, Industrial Relations, Personnel Practices, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Guide of Safety Reference Materials on File at Training Office, 1953; Publication (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Box: 51, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Reference Materials Available from Training Office Production, Community & Public Relations, Employee Relations, Training, 1954; Publication (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Box: 51, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Guide of Safety Reference Materials on File at Training Office, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Guide of Reference Materials on file at Training Office - covering Training, Production, Employee & Public Relations, Industrial Relations, Personnel Practices, 1950; Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Guide of Safety Reference Materials on File at Training Office, 1951; Publication (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Box: 52, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Guide for Safety and Health Reference Materials, 1957; Publication (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Box: 52, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Training Manual, 1949; Publication (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Box: 52, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Training Programs, Publication (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Box: 52, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Reference Materials Available from Training Office - On the Subjects of Training, Production, Employment & Public Relations, Industrial Relations & Personnel Practices, 1953; Publication (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Box: 52, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Guide for Production, Community & Public Relations, Employee Relations - Personnel Practices, and Training Reference Materials, 1957; Publication (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Box: 52, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Outline to a Dynamic Career in Marketing Management, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Your Career With, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Quaker Oats Company Grocery Products Sales Trainee Program, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: New Horizons in Research & Development, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Your Profit Sharing Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Your Group Life Insurance Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Remarks of Robert D. Stuart, Jr., President of The Quaker Oats Company before the New York Society of Security Analysts, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Plan for Progress, 1964; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The Improved Quaker Medical Care Program, 1965; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Your Career With Quaker, Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: 1965 Annual Safety Report (Plant Accident and Fire Experience), 1966; Publication (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Box: 52, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, 1962; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Where Tomorrow Begins, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Grocery Products Sales Trainee Program, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Your Career With The Quaker Oats Company, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Meet the Quaker Oats Family of Quality Products, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The Quaker, 1961; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Arriving At The Quaker Oats Annual Sales Meetings, 1962; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: The Quaker Retirement Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: The Quaker Hospital Care Plan, Publication (Box 52, Folder 7)